Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center Vertical Files, 1916-1999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center Vertical Files 1916-1999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
79.0 linear feet Extent: 56,000 Items
Established in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The Information Center served as a corporate research library and reference center for the agency. Collection spans the years 1916-1999 and consists of subject files containing clippings, published articles, internal documentation, memoranda, research reports and other materials. The bulk of materials originated at the Chicago Office; the Justin White Files arrived from the New York Office. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.00714
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center Vertical Files were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1996 and 2008.
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1916-1999 and consists of subject files containing clippings, published articles, internal documentation, memoranda, research reports and other materials. The bulk of materials originated at the Chicago Office; the Justin White Files arrived from the New York Office.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged into three series: Internal Documentation; Subject Files; and Justin White Files. The Internal Documentation series contains materials relevant to the history and operations of the agency. It includes files on domestic and foreign offices, company organization, and background information on company departments, subsidiaries and parent companies. The Subject Files is a large alphabetical file covering a wide range of topics, from types of advertising to product categories and market demographics. The Justin White Files contain a smaller subject file from the New York Office.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; Advertising -- Research; Advertising -- History; Advertising agencies -- History; Pamphlets; Vertical files; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records
J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising Vertical Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Corporation Vertical Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Information Center Records
J. Walter Thompson Company Marketing Vertical Files
Description of Collection
- Internal Documentation1916-1999 and undated
  - “Went to archives” in 1984, undated (Box 1)
  - Addresses and articles, 1980-1989, (8 folders) (Box 1)
  - Advertising accounts, 1970s, (1 of 9 folders) (Box 1)
  - Advertising accounts, 1970s, (2-9 of 9 folders) (Box 2)
  - Advertising accounts, 1980s, (8 folders) (Box 3)
  - Advertising/Marketing Intelligence, undated (Box 3)
  - Archives, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Art, undated (Box 4)
  - Awards, undated, (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Billings, undated (Box 4)
  - Brouillard Communications, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - The Cable Shop, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Computer installations (Box 4)
  - Corporate communications (sa Brouillard communications), undated (Box 4)
  - Creative Standards Committee (Box 4)
  - Deltakos (Box 5)
  - Direct (incl. Soskin Thompson Associates) (Box 5)
  - Direct response (Box 5)
  - Entertainment group, 1979-1983 (Box 5)
  - Euro-Advertising Agencies (Box 5)
  - Financial aspects
    - JWT, 1969-1979, (11 folders) (Box 5)
    - JWT, 1980-1985, (7 folders) (Box 6)
    - WPP, 1991-1995, (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - Hill and Knowlton, undated, (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - History:
    - General, 1980-1990s, undated, (1-3 of 12 folders) (Box 8)
    - General, 1980-1990s, undated, (4-12 of 12 folders) (Box 9)
    - Ad Age, 1959 (Box 10)
    - C. E. Raymond (Kenneth Ward Edition), undated (Box 10)
    - 100th Anniversary, undated, (4 folders) (Box 10)
    - Organization charts, undated (Box 10)
    - Organizational structure, undated (Box 10)
  - International Department, undated (Box 10)
  - Lansdowne Advertising, undated (Box 10)
  - Learning Series, undated (Box 10)
  - Legal Department, undated (Box 10)
  - Lord, Allen, Federico, undated (Box 10)
  - Management Reference Center, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Management Reference Center, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Media organization:
    - General (Box 11)
    - Media resources and research (Box 11)
    - Programming (Box 11)
    - SPOT Broadcasting Syndication, (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Medical Research Bureau (Box 11)
  - Media research and resources, (6 folders) (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Organizational structure:
    - JWT, pre 1987-1990, (4 folders) (Box 13)
    - WPP, 1987, (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - Public relations (Box 13)
  - Public service activities (Box 13)
  - Soskin Thompson Associates (Box 14)
  - Target Group Index, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Thompson Recruitment Advertising (Box 14)
  - World Wide Agency (see JWT-Thompson Recruitment Advertising) (Box 14)
  - WPP
    - General, 1980s-1990s, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Einson Freeman (Box 14)
  - Atlanta Office
    - General, undated (Box 14)
  - Chicago Office
    - Account Management Assignments, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Account responsibilities, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Advertising Services Management Training Manual (Box 15)
    - Accounts, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Ad Services Department (Box 15)
    - Awards (Box 15)
    - Bloomingdales (Box 15)
    - Consumer Affair (Box 15)
    - Consumer in Crisis Seminar, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Employee Assistance Program (Box 16)
    - Creative Department (Box 16)
    - General files, 1920s-1950s (Box 16)
    - Hancock Center, (2 folders)
      - General, 1960s-1980s, (1-5 of 6 folders) (Box 16)
      - General, 1960s-1980s, (6 of 6 folders) (Box 17)
      - Growth force (Box 17)
    - History:
      - Original (Box 17)
      - Howington, (2 folders) (Box 17)
      - History: (Box 17)
      - History and articles (Box 17)
    - Holidays (Box 17)
    - Home Economic Center (Box 17)
    - Information Center, (2 folders) (Box 18)
      - History: Strable's chronology (Box 18)
      - I.C. memos, 1980-1987, (5 folders) (Box 18)
    - Management (Box 19)
    - Marketing plans, 1970s, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Media Department (Box 19)
    - New Business (Box 19)
    - Personnel, 1980-1990, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box 19)
    - Personnel, 1980-1990, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box 20)
    - Personnel manual, 1990 (Box 20)
    - Public Relations (Box 20)
    - Research Department, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Review Board (Box 20)
    - "State of the Agency" (Box 20)
    - Word Processing Center (Box 20)
  - Denver Office
    - General, undated (Box 20)
  - Detroit Office
    - General, undated (Box 20)
  - Houston Office
    - General, undated (Box 20)
  - Los Angeles Office
    - General, undated (Box 20)
  - Miami Office
    - General, undated (Box 21)
  - San Francisco Office
    - General, undated, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - New York Office:
    - Information Center (Box 21)
    - International Department (Box 21)
    - Legal Department (Box 21)
    - Personnel recruitment ad, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Research Department (Box 21)
  - Philadelphia Office
    - General, undated (Box 21)
  - Washington Office
    - General, undated (Box 21)
  - West (see also JWT/LA & JWT/SFO)
    - General, undated (Box 21)
  - Foreign Offices
    - General, undated, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Asia (Box 21)
    - Australia (Box 21)
    - Canada (Box 21)
    - Frankfurt (Box 21)
    - India (Box 21)
    - Italy (Box 22)
    - London:
      - London Office (Box 22)
      - BMRB (British Market Research Bureau) (Box 22)
      - Information Services (Box 22)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 22)
    - South Africa, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Worldwide Office Address List, (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Company articles, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Chicago (Box 23)
  - Chicago Infocenter: Forms (Box 23)
  - JWT Presentations (Box 23)
  - Source (Box 23)
  - New American Consumer, 1985 (Box 23)
  - WPP (Box 23)
  - WPP Group: Atticus Awards (Box 23)
  - YOU publication (Box 23)
  - Chicago Advertising Process and Procedures, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Recruitment and Advertising (Box 24)
  - The Wire (Box 24)
  - Advertising Process and Procedures Manual, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Chicago Today Magazine, 1971 (Box 25)
  - New York Office, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Accounts (Box 25)
  - Articles distributed by Strouse (Box 25)
  - Creative Library (Box 25)
  - WPP Group:
    - Annual reports, 1990s, (8 folders) (Box 26)
    - Companies Book, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Group Navigator (Box 26)
    - Interim reports (Box 26)
- Subject Files
  - Accidents (Box 27)
  - Advertisements, Classifieds (Box 27)
  - Advertisements, Famous (Box 27)
  - Advertisements-Readership-Articles, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Advertisements-Repetition (Box 27)
  - Advertisers-Agency Relations (Box 27)
  - (See Also: Advertising Agencies-Client Relations) (Box 27)
  - Advertising-Articles, 1950 and before (Box 27)
  - Advertising-Articles, 1970s, (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Advertising-Articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 27)
  - Advertising-Articles, 1990s (Box 27)
  - Advertising Agencies-Articles, 1950s (Box 28)
  - Advertising-Articles, 1960s (Box 28)
  - Advertising Agencies-Articles, 1960s, (4 folders) (Box 28)
  - Advertising Agencies-Articles, 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Advertising Agencies-Articles, 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Advertising Agencies-Articles, 1990s (Box 29)
  - Advertising Agencies-Billings (Box 29)
  - Advertising Agencies-Black Agencies (Box 29)
  - Advertising Agencies-Client Relations, (4 folders) (Box 29)
  - (See Also: Advertisers, Agencies Relations) (Box 29)
  - Advertising Agencies-Compensation, 1980s, (4 folders) (Box 30)
  - Advertising Agencies-Compensation, 1990s, (1-3 of 7 folders) (Box 30)
  - Advertising Agencies-Compensation, 1990s, (4-7 of 7 folders) (Box 31)
  - Advertising Agencies-Financial Aspects (Box 31)
  - Advertising Agencies-House Agencies (Box 31)
  - Advertising Agencies-Personnel, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Advertising Agencies-Ratings, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Advertising Agencies-Self Promotion (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Children (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Environment, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Fear (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Health (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Humor, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Advertising Appeals-Interracial & Ethnic, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Advertising Appeals-Misc. (Box 33)
  - Advertising Appeals-Music, Jingles (Box 33)
  - Advertising Appeals-Patriotic (Box 33)
  - Advertising Appeals-Sex, prior to 1990 (Box 33)
  - Advertising Appeals-Sex, 1990s, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Advertising as a Profession & Career (Box 33)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1950s (Box 33)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1960s, (1 of 4 folders) (Box 33)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1960s, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box 34)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1980s, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Advertising, Attitudes toward-Articles, 1990s (Box 34)
  - Advertising Awards, prior to 1980 (Box 35)
  - Advertising Awards, 1980s, (1-6 of 9 folders) (Box 35)
  - Advertising Awards, 1980s, (7-9 of 9 folders) (Box 36)
  - Advertising Awards, 1990s (Box 36)
  - Advertising Campaigns, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Advertising-Chicago, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Advertising-Chicago, Statistics (Box 37)
  - Advertising-Color (Box 37)
  - Advertising-Commodity (Box 37)
  - Advertising-Continuity & Frequency (Box 37)
  - Advertising-Cooperative (Box 37)
  - Advertising Copy, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Advertising Copy-Brand Comparisons, 1960-1979, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Advertising Copy-Brand Comparisons, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Advertising Copy-Wearout (Box 38)
  - Advertising, Corporate, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Advertising, Costs, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Advertising Expenditures (Box 39)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Budgets, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Budgets-Recession, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Budgets-Recession, (3 of 3 folders) (Box 40)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Statistics, Articles, 1960s and before, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Statistics, Articles, 1970s, (4 folders) (Box 40)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Statistics, Articles, 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Advertising Expenditures-Statistics, Articles, 1990s (Box 40)
  - Advertising-Exposure (Box 40)
  - Advertising, History of, (5 folders) (Box 41)
  - Advertising, Industrial (Box 41)
  - Advertising, International Aspects, 1980s (Box 41)
  - Advertising, International Aspects, 1990s (Box 41)
  - Advertising, Legal Aspects (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Aerial (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Audience Measurement (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Barter (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Interactive (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Research, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Shopping Carts (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Specialty (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Theatre Screen (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Transit (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Video (Box 42)
  - Advertising Media-Yellow Pages/Directories (Box 42)
  - Advertising Council, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Advertising Council-Annual Reports, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Advertising Council-Economic Communicator (Box 43)
  - Advertising Council-Public Service Advertising Bulletin (2 years) (Box 43)
  - Advertising-Crisis (Box 43)
  - Advertising-Economic Aspects, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Advertising Effectiveness, Articles, 1950s (Box 43)
  - Advertising Effectiveness, Articles, 1960s, (4 folders) (Box 44)
  - Advertising Effectiveness, Articles, 1970s, (3 folders) (Box 44)
  - Advertising Effectiveness, Articles, 1980s, (3 folders) (Box 45)
  - Advertising Effectiveness, Articles, 1990s, (3 folders) (Box 45)
  - Advertising Ethics (Box 45)
  - Advertising-Millennium (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Political (Box 46)
  - Advertising-Positioning (Box 46)
  - Advertising-Public Service (Box 46)
  - Advertising-Recall (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Regional (Box 46)
  - Advertising Research (Box 46)
  - Advertising Research Foundation (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Slogans (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Subliminal (Box 46)
  - Advertising-Success Stories, (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Value of, 1980s, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Advertising, Value of, 1980s, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Advertising, Value of, 1990s, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Advertising, Value of-Misc., (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Advertorials (Box 47)
  - Affinity Marketing (Box 47)
  - Air Travel (Box 47)
  - Air Travel-Aircraft (Box 47)
  - Air Travel-Airlines (Box 47)
  - Air Travel-Airlines-Articles (Box 48)
  - Air Travel-Airlines-Food Service (Box 48)
  - Air Travel-Cargo (Box 48)
  - Air Travel-History (Box 48)
  - Air Travel-Safety (Box 48)
  - Alcoholic Beverages (Box 48)
  - Alcoholic Beverages-Advertising (Box 48)
  - Alcoholic Beverages-Historical, (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - AAAA-Account Executive Series, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 48)
  - AAAA-Account Executive Series, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 49)
  - AAAA-General, (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - AAAA-Indexes, 1978-1995, (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - AAAA-NARB (National Advertising Review Board) (Box 49)
  - AAAA-Personnel Studies (Box 50)
  - AAAA-Rosters (Box 50)
  - AAAA-Standards (Box 50)
  - Animation (Box 50)
  - Art & Arts (Box 50)
  - Asian Market (Box 50)
  - Association of National Advertisers (Box 50)
  - Associations-Advertising (Box 50)
  - Automotive Aftermarket (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-Advertising (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-Driving Costs (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-Driving Habits (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-Electric Cars (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-History, (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Automotive Industry-Safety Devices (Box 51)
  - Automotive Industry-Statistics (Box 51)
  - Baby Market (Box 51)
  - Bagels (Box 51)
  - Baking-Home (Box 51)
  - Banks-Advertising (Box 51)
  - Banks & Banking (Box 51)
  - Banks & Banking-Electronic Banking (Box 51)
  - Beverages-Advertising (Box 51)
  - Bicentennial, (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Bicycles (Box 51)
  - Black market (Box 51)
  - Blacks-History, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - (Box 52)
  - Blacks-Statistics (Box 52)
  - Boats & Boating (Box 52)
  - Books (Box 52)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 52)
  - Brand Image (Box 52)
  - Brand Loyalty (Box 52)
  - Brand Managers (Box 52)
  - Brand Names (Box 52)
  - Brands (Box 53)
  - Brands, Advertised (Box 53)
  - Brands, Private Label, (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Brands, Value of, (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Bread-History (Box 53)
  - Breakfasts-Consumer Studies (Box 53)
  - Breakfasts-History (Box 53)
  - Business-American, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Business Failures (Box 54)
  - Business, Small, (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Business, Women (Box 54)
  - Buying Habits (Box 54)
  - Buying Habits, “Buy American” (Box 54)
  - Buying Habits-Food-Recession (Box 54)
  - Canned Foods-History (Box 55)
  - Catalogs (Box 55)
  - Cause Related Marketing (Box 55)
  - Cereal-History (Box 55)
  - Charities, (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Cheese, (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Cheese-Cheddar (Box 55)
  - Cheese-Fondues (Box 55)
  - Cheese-History (Box 55)
  - Cheese-Parmesan (Box 55)
  - Cheese-Roquefort & Blue (Box 55)
  - Cheese-Swiss (Box 55)
  - Chocolate & Cocoa Products (Box 56)
  - Cholesterol, (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - Cigarettes-Advertising (Box 56)
  - Cigarettes-Generic (Box 56)
  - Cigarettes-Health Aspects, (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Cleaning Products-Household Cleaners (Box 56)
  - Clothing-History (Box 57)
  - Cobranding (Box 57)
  - Coffee (Box 57)
  - Coffee-Advertising (Box 57)
  - Coffee-Decaffeinated (Box 57)
  - Coffee-Health Aspects (Box 57)
  - Coffee-History (Box 57)
  - Coffee-Instant (Box 57)
  - Comics (Box 57)
  - Computers-Advertising (Box 57)
  - Computers-Electronic Mail (Box 57)
  - Computers-History (Box 57)
  - Computers-Multimedia (CD-ROMs, etc.) (Box 57)
  - Computers-Networks (mainframes, etc.) (Box 57)
  - Computers, Personal (includes stats.), 1990s on, (4 folders) (Box 58)
  - Computers, Portable (Laptops) (Box 58)
  - Computers-Software (Box 58)
  - Confectionary (Box 58)
  - Confectionary-Advertising (Box 58)
  - Confectionary-Chewing Gum (Box 58)
  - Confectionary-History (Box 58)
  - Conference Board-Business Cycle Indicators (Box 58)
  - Conference Board-Business Executives’ Expectations (Box 58)
  - Conference Board-Conferences/Seminars (Box 58)
  - Conference Board-Consumer Confidence-European Union (Box 58)
  - Conference Board-Consumer Confidence-U.S., Current (2 years) (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Consumer Confidence Survey, Historical, (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Consumer Market Watch (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Consumer Research Center-Background Reports for Sale Pubs. (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Demographics (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Forecasters’ Forecasts (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Int’l Profiles (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Major Metropolitan Market Series, (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Marketing Briefing (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Publications (Box 59)
  - Conference Board-Regional Economies and Markets (Box 60)
  - Conference Board-Special Consumer Survey Report (Box 60)
  - Conference Board-Spending (Box 60)
  - Conference Board-Studies, (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Consumer Electronics, (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Consumer Expenditures (Box 60)
  - Consumer Protection-Articles, 1970s, (6 folders) (Box 61)
  - Consumer Protection-Articles, 1980s (Box 61)
  - Consumer Research (Box 61)
  - Consumers-Millennium (Box 62)
  - Contests (Box 62)
  - Contraceptives, (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Cooking (Box 62)
  - Corporate Image, (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Corporate Image-Corp. vs. Product (Umbrella), (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Coupons-Articles, 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Coupons-Articles, 1980s (Box 63)
  - Coupons-Articles, 1990s (Box 63)
  - Coupons-Consumer Studies (Box 63)
  - Coupons-Redemption, (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Credit Cards, (3 folders) (Box 63)
  - Crime & Criminals (See Also: Geog.-Chicago-Crime) (Box 64)
  - Crisis Advertising (Box 64)
  - Customer Service (Box 64)
  - Dairy-Dairy Council Digest (Box 64)
  - Dairy Industry (Box 64)
  - Dairy Products (Box 64)
  - Dairy Products-Consumption-Historical, (2 folders) (Box 64)
  - Dairy Products-Dips (Box 64)
  - Dairy Products-Statistics (Box 64)
  - Database Marketing (Box 64)
  - Dentistry (Box 64)
  - Diets & Dieting-1970-1989 (Box 64)
  - Diets & Dieting, 1990s (Box 64)
  - Diets & Dieting-Weight Control Aids, 1980s (Box 65)
  - Diets & Dieting-Weight Control Aids, 1990s (Box 65)
  - Digestion (Box 65)
  - Dining Out (Box 65)
  - Direct Mail Advertising (Box 65)
  - Direct Marketing (Box 65)
  - Discount Stores (Box 65)
  - “Do-It-Yourself” Market (Box 65)
  - Drugs-Aspirin (Box 65)
  - Drug Stores (Box 65)
  - Eating Habits (Box 65)
  - Eating Outdoors (Box 65)
  - Ecology, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Ecology, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Economic Conditions, (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Education (Box 66)
  - Education-College Market (Box 66)
  - Eggs (Box 66)
  - Electrical power (Box 66)
  - Electronics, (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Emotions (Box 66)
  - Employees (Box 67)
  - Eyes (Box 67)
  - Facsimile Machines (Box 67)
  - Fads, (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - Fairs & Expositions-Chicago World’s Fair, 1992 (Box 67)
  - Fairs & Expositions-Knoxville World’s Fair, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Fairs & Expositions-New York World’s Fair, 1964 (Box 67)
  - Fashion & Fashion Designers (Box 67)
  - Fats & Oils-Fat Substitutes (Box 67)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago-Economic Perspectives, 1993-1999, (7 folders) (Box 68)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago-Economic Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 68)
  - Financial Services (Box 69)
  - Fireworks (Box 69)
  - Flags (Box 69)
  - Flavor (Box 69)
  - Florist Industry & Trade (Box 69)
  - Flour (Box 69)
  - Flowers & Plants (Box 69)
  - Food Additives (Box 69)
  - Food Advertising (Box 69)
  - Food Consumption-Historical (Box 69)
  - Food, Convenience (Box 69)
  - Food Expenditures-Historical (Box 69)
  - Food, Fad (Box 70)
  - Food, Forum (Box 70)
  - Food-History (Box 70)
  - Food Marketing (Box 70)
  - Food, Nationality-Mexican (Box 70)
  - Food, Natural/Organic (Box 70)
  - Food-Nutritive Value (Box 70)
  - Food-Nutritive Value-Fiber (Box 70)
  - Food Poisoning (Box 70)
  - Food Preservation (Box 70)
  - Food Preservation-Dehydration (Box 70)
  - Food-Private Label (Box 70)
  - Food, Synthetic-Articles, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Foodtalk (Box 70)
  - Foreign Language Market (Box 71)
  - Foundation Garments (Box 71)
  - Franchising (Box 71)
  - Frozen Foods-History (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Apples (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Apricots (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Avocados (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Bananas (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Berries (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Cherries (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Citrus (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Cranberries (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Dried (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Grapes (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Kiwi (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Lemons (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Mangos (Box 71)